<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on SkillScript</title><link>https://leylatheunissen.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on SkillScript</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Leyla Theunissen</copyright><atom:link href="https://leylatheunissen.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://leylatheunissen.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/cover-letter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://leylatheunissen.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/cover-letter/</guid><description>&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="keywords-cover-letteruniversitypersonalization">title: &amp;ldquo;How to Craft a Good Cover Letter&amp;rdquo;
description: &amp;ldquo;Learn what the Columbia University Career Office says about writing a strong cover letter&amp;rdquo;
draft: false
tags: [&amp;ldquo;Featured&amp;rdquo;]
keywords: [&amp;ldquo;cover letter&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;university&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;personalization&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>A well-crafted cover letter can make a significant difference in a job application, providing an opportunity to showcase personality, enthusiasm, and alignment with a role. Columbia University’s Center for Career Education explains the key elements of an effective cover letter, including tailoring content to specific job descriptions, highlighting relevant skills, and demonstrating genuine interest in the company. The guide also offers practical tips for structure, tone, and avoiding common mistakes, making it a valuable resource for job seekers at any stage of their career.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://leylatheunissen.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/github-jobs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://leylatheunissen.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/github-jobs/</guid><description>&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="keywords-jobsnew-gradcareer-tech">title: &amp;ldquo;The Ultimate Resource for 2025 New Grad Job Seekers&amp;rdquo;
description: &amp;ldquo;Browse this repository of entry-level software, tech, CS, PM, and quant jobs for new grads&amp;rdquo;
draft: false
tags: [&amp;ldquo;Featured&amp;rdquo;]
keywords: [&amp;ldquo;jobs&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;new grad&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;career&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;tech&amp;rdquo;]&lt;/h2>
&lt;h1 id="the-ultimate-resource-for-2025-new-grad-job-seekers">The Ultimate Resource for 2025 New Grad Job Seekers&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Breaking into the job market as a new graduate can feel overwhelming. Between crafting the perfect resume, tailoring cover letters, and preparing for technical interviews, there’s a lot to manage. Fortunately, the &lt;strong>&lt;a href="https://github.com/cvrve/New-Grad-2025" target="_blank" rel="noopener">New Grad 2025 GitHub repository&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> by CVRVE is a game-changer for early-career job seekers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>University of Pennsylvania Graduate Outcomes</title><link>https://leylatheunissen.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/penn-statistics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://leylatheunissen.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/penn-statistics/</guid><description>&lt;p>The University of Pennsylvania provides a comprehensive look at post-graduation outcomes, showcasing the diverse career paths its students take. The report highlights employment statistics, industry trends, and further education pursuits, demonstrating Penn graduates&amp;rsquo; strong placement in top firms and graduate programs. It also emphasizes the importance of networking, internships, and Penn’s career services in securing job opportunities. With data-driven insights, the article offers a valuable perspective on how Penn equips students for success beyond college.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>